question_data = {"response_code": 0, "results": [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The word &quot;Inception&quot; came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&zaquot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers",
                                       "question": "DHCP stands for Dynamic Host Configuration Port.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "In 2016, the IUCN reclassified the status of Giant Pandas from endangered to vulnerable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                       "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
